Hanks, Paul; Papers apap253
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
Paul Hanks Papers
1944-1966
Undated
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
apap253
9.9 cubic ft.
Paul B. Hanks Jr.'s papers document his last years as a Republican assemblyman in the New York State Legislature for Monroe County (N.Y.)'s 3rd District (1960-1964).
Collection X
Scope and Contents
This collection contains materials from Paul B. Hanks Jr.'s last years in the New York State Assembly, 1960-1964. In Series 1, Subject Files, the most significant topics include his correspondence and information on the Ways and Means Committee, upon which Hanks served, and constituent correspondence. These correspondences range from letters with the general public ones with companies, schools, and churches. There is much information about education, which includes budget, further education, adult education, and the State University budget.
Series 2, Legislation, consists of legislation introduced in the Assembly by Hanks. There are many memoranda from Hanks to/from outside businesses and associated groups with information on this legislation being introduced.
Please note the collection does not include materials from Hanks' earlier years in the Assembly.
Access
Access to this record group is unrestricted.
Acquisition Information
Paul Hanks initially donated his papers to Syracuse University in 1967. In 2006, all the papers were transferred to the M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives.
Biographical Sketch
Paul B. Hanks Jr. was born on March 4, 1923. He graduated from the University of Rochester with a BA degree. Hanks also graduated from Cornell Law with an LLB. He was also a World War II veteran and served as a radar navigator in the Pacific Theatre. Hanks was a member of the New York State Bar, Harsch-Crisp Seaman Post, No. 379, American Legion, V.F.W., Brockport Volunteer Fire Department, Phi Delta Phi Legal Fraternity and many other organizations.
Constituents from Monroe County's 3rd District elected Hanks to the New York State Assembly in 1952. A Republican, he served in the Assembly until 1964. Hanks served as chair of the Military Affairs Committee and was a member of the Ways and Means Committee, Banks Committee, Canals and Waterways, and Villages Committee. Hanks was also the vice-chair of the Joint Legislative Committee on Unsatisfied Judgment Fund and Compulsory Automobile Insurance and a member of the Joint Legislative Committee on Winter Tourists and Interstate Cooperation.
The Hanks files document his passion for education. There are extensive materials about education budget, further education, adult education, and state university budget. Hanks wanted to give everyone a chance to learn at an affordable price. Not only did he want education to be accessible for adults, but he also wanted the school budgets to be used wisely.
Hanks also was passionate about the alcohol beverage control laws (A.B.C. Laws), and seat belt laws. Hanks compiled countless reports on the effects that alcohol had on young people and how it led to more motor vehicle accidents. Hanks wanted to cut down this effect by changing the A.B.C. laws and by raising the drinking age to 21. Hanks' papers also discuss the elevated damage that not wearing a seatbelt could result with vehicle accidents. Hanks was quite forward-looking with these ideas. The drinking age was not raised to 21 in New York until 1985. The first mandatory seat belt law went into effect in 1984 in New York.
Hanks passed away on September 17, 2002. He was survived by his two sons, daughter, six grandchildren, and one great-grandchild.
Arrangement of the Collection
The collection is organized into the following series: Series 1, Subject Files, and Series 2, Legislation. Both Series 1 and 2 are arranged alphabetically.
Hanks, Paul B. (1923-2002); Politics and Politicians; Politicians--New York (State)
- Subject Files, 1944-1966; Undated; 1; 8.6 cubic ft.
  Scope and Contents
  Series 1 contains Subject Files, which includes correspondence with the general public and organizations, budget information, education information, and information and correspondence about the Ways and Means Committee. There are also assorted newspaper clippings, reports, and notes taken by Hanks.
  Arrangement
  Arranged alphabetically.
  - 5% Take Home Pay for Teachers, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - 17th Annual Legislative Seminar, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - 350th Anniversary Celebration Report, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - "1955 Municipal Legislative Problems" (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - 1960 Annual Report Department of Public Works (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - 1960 Year Book 12th Annual Edition New York Republican State Committee (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - 1961 State Legislative Program of the Liberal Party, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - 1964 Legislative Program of the New York State Association for Retarded Children, Undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - 1964 Poll on Eleven Important Issues (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - A Comparison of the Tax Status, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - A Dangerous Combination, 1961; Undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - A Journal of Church and Society Special Progress, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - A Matter of Necessity: Report No. 22, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - A Review and Appraisal of New York's Low Income Housing Program, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - A Revised Policy on Tuition and Fees in State University of New York, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - A Statement of the Hospital Association of New York State Inc., 1964 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - A World Trade Center in the Port of New York, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - ABC Law (Minimum Drinking Age), 1963 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Accident Facts, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Ad Barram-By Paul L. Bleakley, Undated (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Adult Education, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Advertising Copy of Vote for Republican Candidate, Undated (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - AID to Cities and Economic Growth, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - AID to Education (1 of 2), 1960-1961; Undated (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - AID to Education (2 of 2), 1960-1962; Undated (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Albany State Telephone Directory: Direct Inward Dialing, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Albany State Telephone Directory, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Alphabetical List of Republican Members, Undated (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Alphabetical List-Assembly Members, Undated (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Amends the Education Law, Undated (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - An Open Letter: To the Governors and Representatives of the Sovereign States, Undated (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Analysis in Question and Answer Form of New York State Licensing Proposal, Undated (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Annual Report 1960: Civil Defense Commission (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Annual Report: Department of Commerce, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Annual Report Department of Works, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Annual Report Power Authority of the State of New York, 1961 February 26 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Annual Report-State Comptroller, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Annual Report State of New York Department of Commerce, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Annual Report of the Comptroller State of New York, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Annual Report of the State Advisory Council on Employment and Unemployment Insurance, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Annual Report of the State Advisory Council on Employment and Unemployment Insurance, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Annual Report of the State Commission Against Discrimination, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Annual Report of the Superintendent of Banks", 1960 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Annual Report Waterfront Commission of New York, 1962-1963 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Anti-Strike Breaker Bill, 1964; Undated (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Assembly Art Exhibit (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Assembly Conference Agenda, 1963 January 9 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Assembly Resolution 96', 1963 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Associated Industries of New York Inc., Undated (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Attorney General's Committee on Human Relations, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Automobile License Fee Correspondence (1 of 2), 1963; Undated (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Automobile License Fee Correspondence (2 of 2), 1963; Undated (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Automobile License Fee-Information, 1963; Undated (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Baldwin vs. City of Buffalo, Undated (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Banks, 1962-1963; Undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Banks and the Future of New York State, Undated (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Banks Committee, 1961; Undated (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Banks Committee, 1964; Undated (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Banks Committee Meetings, 1964; Undated (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Bill Boards, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Birth Control, 1963-1964 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Boat Registration Fees, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Branch Bank Bill, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Brockport Central Committee Report Notes, Undated (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Budget, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Budget, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Budget Bill Transcription, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Bulletin from New York State Council of Retail Merchants, 1961; 1964 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Business Book 1963 Buffalo Area (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Business Fact Book, 1963 Nassau-Suffolk District (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Business Fact Book, 1963 New York City (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Business Fact Book, 1963 Westchester-Rockland County District (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Business in New York, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Business in New York State, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Business Trends in New York State, 1961 May 5 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Campaign Bullets, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Canals and Waterways Committee, Undated (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Cardiovascular Health Center, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Catalog of Republican Campaign Materials, Undated (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Catastrophic Health Insurance, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Central Bureau for the Jewish Aged, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Champlain Valley Special Teacher Association, 1963 May 5 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Change in Senate Calendar, Undated (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Chattel Mortgages, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - China Medicine Massage Clinic, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Chiropractors (1 of 2), 1963; 1961; Undated (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Chiropractors (2 of 2), 1963; 1961; 1964; Undated (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Chronic Disease Research Institute Research Report, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Citizens Public Expenditure Survey, Inc., 1963 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - City of Rochester, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - City of Rochester Letters, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Civil Rights and Federal Powers, Undated (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Civil Service, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Civil War Centennial Commission, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Civil War Centennial Commission, 1962-1963 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Clerks Office Board of Supervisors, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Clinical, Bioanalytical Laboratories and Licensing, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Closed Invitations, 1963-1964; Undated (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Conservation Department Reports, 1956; 1963 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Correspondence About Legislation, 1963-1964 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Correspondence from the Commissioner of Education, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Correspondence with General Public, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Collective Bargaining-Hospitals, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Commission on Uniform State Laws, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Committee List, 1960-1961; Undated (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Complete Review of Fiscal Polices of New York, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Congratulations, 1960-1961 (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Conservative Party of New York State, Undated (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Construction Craftsman, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - Contact Lenses, 1961; 1963 (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - Copy of Brief in Support of the Cook-Brook Bill, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - Correspondence to Hanks, 1962-1964 (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - Correspondence with the New York State Association Chiefs of Police, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - CSS: Special Report: 1964 Legislative Recommendations, Undated (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - County of Monroe, 1963; Undated (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - Current Economic Trends and Their Impact on Business, 1960 December 26 (Box 2, Folder 66)
  - Current Resolutions of the Association: Report No. 23, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 67)
  - Cycle Billing, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 68)
  - Dairy Industry, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 69)
  - Death or Life: Report on Motor Vehicles and Traffic Safety, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 70)
  - Department of Welfare Bureau of Child Welfare, 1962-1963 (Box 2, Folder 71)
  - Dick Bartlett's Report from Albany, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 72)
  - Discovery and Use of Talent, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 73)
  - Division of Alcoholic Beverage Control, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 74)
  - Division of the Treasury Report for 1959-1960, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 75)
  - "Do We Want Morons?", 1964 (Box 2, Folder 76)
  - Dog Race Legalization, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 77)
  - Draft of a Letter from Sam W. Ingram, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 78)
  - Economic Basis is for Port Performance Appraisal, Undated (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Editorial Public Affairs, 1964 January 7 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Education (1 of 2), 1960-1964 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Education (2 of 2), 1960-1964; Undated (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Education Correspondence, 1961; 1963-1964; Undated (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Education Correspondence, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Education in New York State, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Education Statistic New York State, 1961; 1964 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Education and Industrial Development, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Educational Television, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Elmira Association of Commerce, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Erie Lackawanna Railroad Company, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Estate Tax, 1964; Undated (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Estimate for a Typical Meat Wholesaler, Undated (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Estimated Expenditure Cuts by Legislature, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Ethics, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Expert from Editorial in New York herald Tribune, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Extending College Opportunity, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - "Facts" (1 of 4), 1964 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - "Facts" (2 of 4), 1964 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - "Facts" (3 of 4), 1964 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - "Facts" (4 of 4), 1964 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Facts 1965-Health (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Facts About Vocational Rehabilitation, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Familial Responsibility and Public Welfare, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Federal Reserve Bank of New York, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Fifth Preliminary Report to the Legislature, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Fiscal Independence, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Fiscal Independence Bill, 1961; 1963 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Fiscal Independence for the 'Big Six" Schools, 1964; Undated (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - For Your Information, 1960-1961 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Franchise Protection, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - "From P. H. Bradley", 1964 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Full Crew, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Full Crew Law, 1964; Undated (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - General Building Contractors, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Governor Rockefeller's Fiscal Integrity Fact or Fraud?, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Guiding Principles for Agreements Between General Hospitals and Long Term Care Facilities, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Guns, 1963-1964; Undated (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Hanks Phone Number Change, Undated (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Higher Education, 1961; 1964-1966 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - "Higher Education in the State of New York", 1963 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Highways, 1963-1964 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Home Builders Association Correspondence to Hanks, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Hospital Forum, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - How a Highway is Born, Undated (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - How Legislators Did Not Represent Their Constituents, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - How the New York State Labor Law Protects You, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - How to Master the Techniques of Winning Elections, Undated (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - Humane Slaughter, 1961; 1963-1964; Undated (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Hunter Mountain, 1961 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Index to Office of Legislative Research Publications, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Informational Leaflet, Division of Conservation Education, Undated (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Inside Report: New York's Political Snake Pit, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Interim Report on the Activities of the Commission, 1955 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Interstate Cooperation JLC, 1963; Undated (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Invitations-Closed (1 of 2), 1962; Undated (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Invitations-Closed (2 of 2), 1962; Undated (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Invitations-Closed, 1963; Undated (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Invitations-Open, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Joint Legislative Committee Report, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Judicial Conference (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Judicial Conference of the State of New York, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Juvenile Trials, 1963-1964; Undated (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Kangaroo Court Provision, 1961 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Knickerbocker Jai-Lai, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Know Your Legislators, 1961; Undated (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Korean War Bonus, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Labor Law-Non-Profit: Campus, etc.., 1961 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Labor Legislation, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Law Students: Part Time Work, 1962-1963 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Lawyers Registration Fee, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Lean on Newsletter, Undated (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Legal Age for Drinking, 1961; Undated (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Legislative Alert, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Legislative Bill Drafting Commission, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Legislative Briefs, 1960-1961 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Legislative Bulletin the Hospital Association of New York State, 1961; 1964 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Legislative Directory of New York State, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Legislative Hopper, 1960-1961; 1964 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Legislative Newsletter New York State Automobile Association, 1961; 1964 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Legislative Program: Broadening the Impact of the Experience Rating, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Legislative Report from Assembly Richard C. Lounsberry, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Legislative Trends, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Lets Modernize Our Horse and Buggy Election Laws, Undated (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Letter About Tuition in State College, Undated (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Letter to Constituents about Aid to Higher Education, 1961 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Letter to Governor Rockefeller, Undated (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Letter to the Legislature from Nelson Rockefeller, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Liberty, 1964 Jan-Feb (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Liberty Amendment, 1962-1963; Undated (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Licensing Collection Agencies, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Licensing of X-Ray Technicians, 1960-1961; Undated (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Liquor and Alcohol Information, Undated (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Liquor Tax File-Correspondence, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Liquor Tax File-Information, 1963; Undated (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - List of the Members of the Legislature of New York, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - Local Assistance Fund, Undated (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - Locations of Main Office and Branches of Commercial Bands, Undated (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - Long Live the American Jury, 1964; Undated (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - Long Range Goals and Legislative Program, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - Major Study of Branch Banking and Bank Mergers, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - Map of New Jersey Public Market Commission, Undated (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - Materials for 1964 New York Elections, Undated (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - Mayor's Citizen's Committee on Off Track Betting Final Report, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 56)
  - McKinney's Session Law News of New York, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - Meat Inspection Program, 1963; Undated (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - Medical Society of the County of Monroe, Inc. Correspondence with Hanks, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 59)
  - Memorandum, 1964; Undated (Box 4, Folder 60)
  - Memorandum of Objects X-Ray Technology Bill, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Memorandum: Senator Keating's Records, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Memo From Assemblyman Fred W. Preller, 1964; Undated (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Mental Illness, 1964; Undated (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Michael Keating Broadcast, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Military Affairs, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Military Affairs Committee, 1944-1945; 1949; 1964; Undated (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Military Affairs Committee, 1963; Undated (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Military Funding, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Minimum Salary for Teachers, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Minimum Wage Laws, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Minority Report of Select Committee on Off Track Betting, Undated (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence (1 of 2), 1961; Undated (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence (2 of 2), 1961; Undated (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Miscellaneous Education Information, 1963-1965; Undated (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Mon. Co. Port Authority, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Monroe County Estimated Expenditures, Undated (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Monroe County Republican Committee, Undated (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Monroe County Republican News Release, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Moreland Commission, 1964; Undated (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Motor Vehicles, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Municipal Cooperation, A Digest of New York State Law, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Municipal Legislation Service, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Municipal Legislative Service of the New York State Conference of Mayors and Other Municipal Officials, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Museums, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Nassau County Republican Committee, Undated (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - National Federation of Independent Business, Undated (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - New Ward and District Arrangement, Undated (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - New York Business Development Corporation, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - New York Business Development Corporation, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - New York Chamber of Commerce, Undated (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - New York City, Background to the 1964-65 Budget, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - New York Job Development Authority, Financial Information, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - New York Metropolitan Council American Jewish Congress, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - New York Republican Report, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - New York State ALF-CIO News, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - New York State and Local Sales Tax Information, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - New York State Announces Opportunities in…, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - New York State Assembly-1964 Resolution No. 47 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - New York State Assembly Telephone Directory, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - New York State Association of Real-Estate Boards Inc., 1964 (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - New York State Bar Association, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - New York State Bar Association Committee on State Legislation, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - New York State Budget. New York Chamber of Commerce, Undated (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - New York State Canners and Freezers Directory, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - New York State Congress of Parents and Teachers, Inc. Action Program of Legislation State Program, 1961 January 16 (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - New York State Council of Retail Merchants Inc., Undated (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - New York State Department of Commerce International Commerce Division a Progress Report, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - New York State Department of Commerce: List of Publications, Undated (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - New York State Department of Motor Vehicles Annual Report, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - New York State Employees, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 52)
  - New York State Examinations, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 53)
  - New York State Help for You College Education, 1963-1964 (Box 5, Folder 54)
  - New York State Senate Special Committee on Smoking and Health, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 55)